
export const quizQuestions_5 = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Which array method is used to iterate over each element and return a new array with modified elements?',
      choices: ['map()', 'filter()', 'reduce()', 'forEach()'],
      correctAnswer: 'map()',
    },
    {
      question: 'What does the filter() method do in JavaScript arrays?',
      choices: ['Modifies each element of the array', 'Creates a new array with elements that pass a test', 'Reduces the array to a single value', 'Iterates over each element without modification'],
      correctAnswer: 'Creates a new array with elements that pass a test',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which array method is used to sort the elements of an array?',
      choices: ['sort()', 'order()', 'arrange()', 'shuffle()'],
      correctAnswer: 'sort()',
    },
    {
      question: 'What does the reduce() method do in JavaScript arrays?',
      choices: ['Modifies each element of the array', 'Creates a new array with elements that pass a test', 'Reduces the array to a single value', 'Iterates over each element without modification'],
      correctAnswer: 'Reduces the array to a single value',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which array method is used to add new elements to the end of an array?',
      choices: ['push()', 'append()', 'add()', 'concat()'],
      correctAnswer: 'push()',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of the splice() method in JavaScript arrays?',
      choices: ['To remove elements from an array', 'To add elements to an array', 'To sort the elements of an array', 'To concatenate two arrays'],
      correctAnswer: 'To remove elements from an array',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which array method is used to check if at least one element in the array satisfies a condition?',
      choices: ['some()', 'any()', 'check()', 'exists()'],
      correctAnswer: 'some()',
    },
    {
      question: 'What does the forEach() method do in JavaScript arrays?',
      choices: ['Modifies each element of the array', 'Creates a new array with elements that pass a test', 'Executes a provided function once for each array element', 'Reduces the array to a single value'],
      correctAnswer: 'Executes a provided function once for each array element',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which array method is used to remove the last element from an array?',
      choices: ['remove()', 'pop()', 'delete()', 'trim()'],
      correctAnswer: 'pop()',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of the indexOf() method in JavaScript arrays?',
      choices: ['To find the index of the first occurrence of a specified element', 'To determine if an element exists in the array', 'To concatenate two arrays', 'To sort the elements of an array'],
      correctAnswer: 'To find the index of the first occurrence of a specified element',
    },
  ],
}